export let questionsArray=[
  {
    question:"Q1: what is the useState hook used for",
    answer:0,
    guessArray:[
      "Dynamically manipulating the DOM",
      "",
      "Hooking the useabilty of className",
      "Creating an element forbackend"
    ]
  },
////////////////////////Question-1 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
  {
    question:"Q2: what does JSX stand for",
    answer:2,
    guessArray:[
      "",
      "Javascript Series X",
      "Javascript XML",
      "Java Syntax X-factor"
    ]
  },
////////////////////////Question-2 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
  {
    question:"Q3: what hook is used for state management ",
    answer:0,
    guessArray:[
      "useReducer",
      "useState",
      "",
      "useContext"
    ]
  },
////////////////////////Question-3 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
{
  question:"Q4: react is a javascript..",
  answer:2,
  guessArray:[
    "",
    "frame Work",
    "library",
    "add-on"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-4 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
{
  question:"Q5: react uses",
  answer:3,
  guessArray:[
    "array components",
    "string components",
    "",
    "fuctional components"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-5 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
{
  question:"Q6: What problem does useContext solve ",
  answer:1,
  guessArray:[
    "helps update inline styles color ",
    "Stops prop drilling",
    "explains context in a story",
    ""
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-6 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////
{
  question:"Q7: What does S.A.P stand for ",
  answer:0,
  guessArray:[
    "Single Page Application",
    "",
    "Sytax Portioned Application",
    "Serious Proper Application"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-7 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"Q8: useEffect is used to.. ",
  answer:3,
  guessArray:[
    "",
    "Effect the DOM ",
    "be effective with classes",
    "eliminate side-effects"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-8 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"Q9: JSX allows you to.. ",
  answer:2,
  guessArray:[
    "add multiple id atrributes",
    "use react without a transpiler",
    "write HTML within JavaScript",
    ""
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-9 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"Q9: 'npx creat-react-app .' offers",
  answer:3,
  guessArray:[
    "a reactive database",
    "a great middleware solution",
    "",
    "a quick startup build of react"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-10 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////


{
  question:"React is a free and opne-source front-end....",
  answer:0,
  guessArray:[
    "JavaScript library",
    "Bootstrap library",
    "CSS library",
    ""
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-11 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"React was initially released in....",
  answer:1,
  guessArray:[
    "",
    "May 29,2013",
    "arpil 29,2013",
    "Dec 29,2013"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-12 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"what is used to increase performance",
  answer:3,
  guessArray:[
    "Virtual Reality",
    "",
    "Original DOM",
    "Virtual DOM"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-13 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"Babel is a ??",
  answer:1,
  guessArray:[
    "interpreter",
    "Transpiler",
    "Compliler",
    ""
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-14 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"how many elements can react component return",
  answer:2,
  guessArray:[
    "3",
    "",
    "1",
    "any"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-15 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

{
  question:"In react what is used to pass data down a component" ,
  answer:0,
  guessArray:[
    "props",
    "renderer",
    "",
    "setState"
  ]
},
////////////////////////Question-16 ^^^^^///////////////////////////////

]